https://www.celine.com/en-us/cookie-policy.html

COOKIES POLICYOfficial website | CELINE
Skip to main content
SKIP TO MAIN NAVIGATION
SKIP TO FOOTER
Your browser's Javascript functionality is turned off. Please turn it on so that you can experience the full capabilities of this site.
COVID-19: SELECT STORES HAVE REOPENED AND ARE NOW OFFERING CURBSIDE PICKUP OR IN-STORE PICKUP. CLICK HERE FOR DETAILS. OUR ONLINE STORE REMAINS OPEN.
Close
We updated our Privacy Policy and our Cookie Policy.
We use cookies, including third-party cookies, for operational purposes, for statistical analysis, to display personalized content, to display advertising targeted to your interests and to analyze the performance of our advertising campaigns. Cookies are also used to control your payments through our anti-fraud provision. By continuing to browse the site, you agree to our use of  cookies.
I AGREE
Menu
SHOPPING BAG 0
0
Shopping bag (0)
Menu
Find in store
CLOSE
CELINE SHOP WOMEN
CELINE 16 STRAP
NEW WINTER PART 2
READY TO WEAR
DRESSES & SKIRTS
0
Shopping bag (0)
back
Search
Submit your Search
CLOSE
Clear
LEGAL NOTICE
TERMS OF USE
PRIVACY POLICY
COOKIES POLICY
active
Sites-Celine_US_V2-Site
Last update on 6/06/2018
See the previous version of this policy
1. WHAT IS A COOKIE ?
A cookies or tracer is a general term for a text file saved in dedicated space on the devices’ hard drive (for example computer, tablet, smartphone, etc.) when you view content or online advertising. This Cookie file allows its issuers to identify the device on which it is stored for as long as the Cookie is valid or stored, that means 13 months maximum. Therefore, cookies do not identify you directly.
Information about your browsing on our site are saved in cookies files installed on your device and allow us to track your activity and to recall information, such as user preferences or information the user previously entered in forms.
2. NOTICE ABOUT COOKIES ON OUR SITE
When you visit our Site for the first time and CELINE intends to place Cookies, we inform you that we use Cookies on an informational banner at the top of the page. When managing your choices about Cookies or by default when continuing to browse the site, you consent to our use of these Cookies.
However, you can change the settings for these cookies at any time. Below you fill find further information about cookies and how you can manager their settings.
3. COOKIES USED ON OUR SITE
When you connect to our site, we may install diverse types of cookies on your device:
Technical cookies to notably allow to:
• adjust the site’s appearance to your device display preferences (for example language used, display resolution or exploitation system used) when you visit our site depending on the materials and viewing software or player software your device contain),
• implement security measure, such as when you are asked to sign in again to a piece of content or service after a certain amount of time;
• give you access to reserved and personal areas of our Site, such as your account using IDs and date that you may have given us previously;
• storing information about a form that you have filled in on our site (account registration or access) or to products, services or information that you have chosen on our site (service subscribed, the content of an order basket).
Audience measurements cookies that allow to:
• obtain visitor statistics and volumes and use of the various elements that make up our Site (sections and contents visited, journeys) to help us improve interest in and the use-friendliness of our services;
Advertising cookies that allow us to:
• to the extent that you have provided us with personal data, including your electronic contact information, during your registration, your Order or your access to one of our services, associating this data with browsing information to, for example, send you electronic marketing messages or display on your device, within advertising spaces that we publish, personalised advertisements that are specifically intended for you that may be of interest to you personally;
Payment security cookies that allow us to:
• help fight against online fraud (payment fraud, identity theft, etc.). Therefore, in accordance with your rights, CELINE or service providers acting on our behalf may store trackers to collect information about the device that made the Order (including the operating system used, the location of the machine, whether or not a proxy was used, etc.). These "fingerprint" trackers associated with your Order data are used to confirm your Order, the payment method used and your delivery method.
Your browsing data is linked to your profile no matter the device used thanks to cookie exchange technology so that your journey can be tracked whatever the device or medium used.
4. LIST OF COOKIES USED:
SFCC
All countries
dwanonymous_*
dwsid
sid
dwsecuretoken_*
dwcustomer_*
dw_cookies_accepted
dw_TLSWarning
dw
Analytics cookies :
SFCC
All countries
dw_dnt*
dwac_*
dwpersonalization_*
dwsourcecode_*
Cookies to improve user experience (for display and results customization purposes):
SFCC
All countries
cqcid
cquid
__cq_uuid
__cqact
__cqviews
__cqsviews
Your choices about cookies
Any cookie placed on your Terminal is subject to your consent which you may express and freely review at any time using the possibilities described above.
There are various ways to manage your cookie options.
You can deactivate each cookie with the specific deactivation link meant for that purpose or use advertising cookie management tools provided by third parties.
Your browser may allow you to choose to disable all or some cookies, either systematically or according to the publisher. You can also configure your browser software to accept or reject cookies (case by case or all).
If you consent to cookies files on your device, cookies embedded on the pages and contents you have viewed will be stored in a dedicated area of your device and will be readable and recognizable only by the issuer.
Consequences of blocking the cookies
Disabling cookies will prevent you from using our site under normal conditions, except for basic functions:
Cookies needed: you may not be able to access the site or its services;
Personalisation Cookies: the site’s presentation does not adapt to the display preferences of your device, your passwords and information about forms filled on the site are not saved,
Audience measurement cookies: has no consequence on the use of website;
Advertising cookies: has no consequence on the use of the website. However, deleting them does not stop online advertising. It will only cause advertising to be shown that does not take your centres of interest into account.
Online payment security cookies: has no consequence on the use of website. However, in case you are trying to buy something online using your credit card, your payment could be delayed because of the need for a manual validation.
Cookie management Tools
Using deactivation links
Purpose
Publisher
Deactivation link
Audience measurement
Google Analytics
Click here
Advertising
Microsoft (Bing ads)
Click here
Using your browser
Each browser software allows you different types of configuration. It will be described the « Help » section of your browser:
If you are using the Internet Explorer browser: click the Tools button and then Internet Options. On the General tab, Browsing History, click Settings. Then, click View Files and select it or the Cookies that you want to disable. Then, close the window that contains the list of Cookies and click OK twice to return to the Internet.
If you are using the Firefox browser: click the Firefox Menu icon, then the Tools button, then Options; in the window that appears, choose Privacy and click Remove Specific Cookies. Select the Cookies that you want to disable then delete them.
If you are using the Safari browser: click the Settings button and then Preferences. In the window that opens, select Privacy/Security then click on Show Cookies. Select the Cookies that you want to disable then click on Delete or Delete all.
If you are using the Chrome browser: click the Google Chrome menu icon, then Settings. At the bottom of the page, click Show advanced settings. In the Privacy section, click Content setting. To deactivate cookies:
Select Cookies, click All Cookies and Site Data, then hover over the site that created the Cookie, and click X in the right corner, or click Remove All.
In the event that you share the use of your Terminal with more than one person, or if your Terminal has several browsers, we cannot be sure that the advertising intended for your Terminal are in keeping with your own use of this Terminal and not that of another user of this Terminal. In this case, sharing with others the use of your Terminal and configuring the settings for cookies is your free choice and responsibility.
TRANSFERRING PERSONAL DATA OUTSIDE THE EUROPEAN UNION
Please note that since some of our digital advertising partners are located outside the European Union, data collected using cookies may be transferred to non-EU member countries, whose personal data protection legislation differs from that applicable in France. We strictly require our partners to use the information collected using Cookies on our Site solely to administer or provide the services requested and ask them to always act in accordance with applicable data protection laws and to pay particular attention to the confidentiality of the information transmitted. To find out more, please refer to their policy on protecting personal data.
Terms and Conditions of Sale
Supply Chain Transparency Act
COOKIES POLICYOfficial website | CELINE
Last update on 6/06/2018
See the previous version of this policy
1. WHAT IS A COOKIE ?
A cookies or tracer is a general term for a text file saved in dedicated space on the devices’ hard drive (for example computer, tablet, smartphone, etc.) when you view content or online advertising. This Cookie file allows its issuers to identify the device on which it is stored for as long as the Cookie is valid or stored, that means 13 months maximum. Therefore, cookies do not identify you directly.
Information about your browsing on our site are saved in cookies files installed on your device and allow us to track your activity and to recall information, such as user preferences or information the user previously entered in forms.
2. NOTICE ABOUT COOKIES ON OUR SITE
When you visit our Site for the first time and CELINE intends to place Cookies, we inform you that we use Cookies on an informational banner at the top of the page. When managing your choices about Cookies or by default when continuing to browse the site, you consent to our use of these Cookies.
However, you can change the settings for these cookies at any time. Below you fill find further information about cookies and how you can manager their settings.
3. COOKIES USED ON OUR SITE
When you connect to our site, we may install diverse types of cookies on your device:
Technical cookies to notably allow to:
• adjust the site’s appearance to your device display preferences (for example language used, display resolution or exploitation system used) when you visit our site depending on the materials and viewing software or player software your device contain),
• implement security measure, such as when you are asked to sign in again to a piece of content or service after a certain amount of time;
• give you access to reserved and personal areas of our Site, such as your account using IDs and date that you may have given us previously;
• storing information about a form that you have filled in on our site (account registration or access) or to products, services or information that you have chosen on our site (service subscribed, the content of an order basket).
Audience measurements cookies that allow to:
• obtain visitor statistics and volumes and use of the various elements that make up our Site (sections and contents visited, journeys) to help us improve interest in and the use-friendliness of our services;
Advertising cookies that allow us to:
• to the extent that you have provided us with personal data, including your electronic contact information, during your registration, your Order or your access to one of our services, associating this data with browsing information to, for example, send you electronic marketing messages or display on your device, within advertising spaces that we publish, personalised advertisements that are specifically intended for you that may be of interest to you personally;
Payment security cookies that allow us to:
• help fight against online fraud (payment fraud, identity theft, etc.). Therefore, in accordance with your rights, CELINE or service providers acting on our behalf may store trackers to collect information about the device that made the Order (including the operating system used, the location of the machine, whether or not a proxy was used, etc.). These "fingerprint" trackers associated with your Order data are used to confirm your Order, the payment method used and your delivery method.
Your browsing data is linked to your profile no matter the device used thanks to cookie exchange technology so that your journey can be tracked whatever the device or medium used.
4. LIST OF COOKIES USED:
SFCC
All countries
dwanonymous_*
dwsid
sid
dwsecuretoken_*
dwcustomer_*
dw_cookies_accepted
dw_TLSWarning
dw
Analytics cookies :
SFCC
All countries
dw_dnt*
dwac_*
dwpersonalization_*
dwsourcecode_*
Cookies to improve user experience (for display and results customization purposes):
SFCC
All countries
cqcid
cquid
__cq_uuid
__cqact
__cqviews
__cqsviews
Your choices about cookies
Any cookie placed on your Terminal is subject to your consent which you may express and freely review at any time using the possibilities described above.
There are various ways to manage your cookie options.
You can deactivate each cookie with the specific deactivation link meant for that purpose or use advertising cookie management tools provided by third parties.
Your browser may allow you to choose to disable all or some cookies, either systematically or according to the publisher. You can also configure your browser software to accept or reject cookies (case by case or all).
If you consent to cookies files on your device, cookies embedded on the pages and contents you have viewed will be stored in a dedicated area of your device and will be readable and recognizable only by the issuer.
Consequences of blocking the cookies
Disabling cookies will prevent you from using our site under normal conditions, except for basic functions:
Cookies needed: you may not be able to access the site or its services;
Personalisation Cookies: the site’s presentation does not adapt to the display preferences of your device, your passwords and information about forms filled on the site are not saved,
Audience measurement cookies: has no consequence on the use of website;
Advertising cookies: has no consequence on the use of the website. However, deleting them does not stop online advertising. It will only cause advertising to be shown that does not take your centres of interest into account.
Online payment security cookies: has no consequence on the use of website. However, in case you are trying to buy something online using your credit card, your payment could be delayed because of the need for a manual validation.
Cookie management Tools
Using deactivation links
Purpose
Publisher
Deactivation link
Audience measurement
Google Analytics
Click here
Advertising
Microsoft (Bing ads)
Click here
Using your browser
Each browser software allows you different types of configuration. It will be described the « Help » section of your browser:
If you are using the Internet Explorer browser: click the Tools button and then Internet Options. On the General tab, Browsing History, click Settings. Then, click View Files and select it or the Cookies that you want to disable. Then, close the window that contains the list of Cookies and click OK twice to return to the Internet.
If you are using the Firefox browser: click the Firefox Menu icon, then the Tools button, then Options; in the window that appears, choose Privacy and click Remove Specific Cookies. Select the Cookies that you want to disable then delete them.
If you are using the Safari browser: click the Settings button and then Preferences. In the window that opens, select Privacy/Security then click on Show Cookies. Select the Cookies that you want to disable then click on Delete or Delete all.
If you are using the Chrome browser: click the Google Chrome menu icon, then Settings. At the bottom of the page, click Show advanced settings. In the Privacy section, click Content setting. To deactivate cookies:
Select Cookies, click All Cookies and Site Data, then hover over the site that created the Cookie, and click X in the right corner, or click Remove All.
In the event that you share the use of your Terminal with more than one person, or if your Terminal has several browsers, we cannot be sure that the advertising intended for your Terminal are in keeping with your own use of this Terminal and not that of another user of this Terminal. In this case, sharing with others the use of your Terminal and configuring the settings for cookies is your free choice and responsibility.
TRANSFERRING PERSONAL DATA OUTSIDE THE EUROPEAN UNION
Please note that since some of our digital advertising partners are located outside the European Union, data collected using cookies may be transferred to non-EU member countries, whose personal data protection legislation differs from that applicable in France. We strictly require our partners to use the information collected using Cookies on our Site solely to administer or provide the services requested and ask them to always act in accordance with applicable data protection laws and to pay particular attention to the confidentiality of the information transmitted. To find out more, please refer to their policy on protecting personal data.
Location
United States
- choose your country
Language
English
Sitemap
Contact us
Legal Terms
Congo (Brazzaville)
Congo (Kinshasa)
Saint Martin (french part)
Sint Maarten (dutch part)
I HAVE READ, UNDERSTOOD AND AGREE TO THE PRIVACY AND DATA PROTECTION POLICY
PLEASE NOTE THAT CHANGING YOUR LOCATION WILL REMOVE ALL ITEMS FROM YOUR ORDER
